newbizine.com 2011-09-13

# Privacy Policy | Business Article Directory

****  
We look forward to receiving your articles, but we DO NOT under any circumstances accept submissions from bots or services we have not approved. The captcha is there to prove you are human. Any attempts to bypass it using automated services is a blatant disregard for our Terms of Service and will be dealt with accordingly. Please be sure you agree with these terms prior to signing up.

 **Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy addresses the handling of any and all personal information that is recorded via author profile or when you submit an article. 

Information collected outside of that supplied by you in your contact details and author profile is limited to IP address and the date of your request or submission.

The privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the web site, nor does it extend to people that the website does not employ or manage. 

**Author Anonymity**  
The website does not provide or guarantee author anonymity. Users must agree that they are aware that any and all personal information provided to the website may be visible to the general public at any time; and therefore should take precaution in what data is provided.

Personal details provided and shown on the website are always the responsibility of the providing party. 

**Information Security and Disclosure**  
Your email address and contact information is stored in a secure database. It is never sold or released without your consent. The website does however maintain the right to contact you when necessary. By providing your contact information, you hereby give permission for the website and its owners/employees to contact you via email. 

**Information Use**  
As a registered user of the website, you are entering into a business relationship whereby the website provides promotion of your article content. In exchange, the website reserves the right to contact you via the email address supplied to notify you of changes to the website or service; to provide useful information; and to send announcements of offers and promotions on behalf of our advertisers and partners.

You may request to be removed from the mailing list at any time, by replying to the received email or clicking on the unsubscribe link when supplied.

At the sole discretion of website management, any and all spam complaints may result in membership termination. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
The website retains the right to change the privacy policy from time to time. It is your responsibility to review the policy from time to time and be aware of any changes. 

Last updated Tue, 10 May 2011 02:59
